https://aptasiapacific.com.au/privacy-and-terms/

Privacy Policy & Terms and Conditions - APT Asia Pacific
Skip to content
Search for:
LigaTurf® HB250
The best value AFL playing surface suitable for all levels of play.
LigaTurf® HB260
The best value AFL playing surface suitable for all levels of play.
LigaTurf® RS+260 COOLplus
Our "One Turf" system provides the best solution for Rugby for both professional and training facilities. Suitable for Soccer and AFL.
Rekortan® G-13
Our top performing, elite full PUR system made from environmentally, renewable resources.
Rekortan® M99
Our top performing full pour system with a focus on energy enhancement for elite athletes and project longevity
Spurtan® BV
Our our most popular, cost effective athletics surface has excellent performance for training and competition, ideal for jumps and run-up facilities.
Spurtan® BS
Our budget solution for athletics, perfect for run-ups and athletics facilities, ideal for multisports.
Spurtan® BSS
Our budget solution for athletics, perfect for run-ups and athletics facilities, ideal for multisports.
Spurtan® WT
The perfect all-rounder, this systems is perfect jogging tracks and athletic activities, easy and fast to install.
Supergrasse® Baseball
Low maintenance All year round playing advantage Extremely popular with coaches and athletes Tailor your Supergrasse field to meet your needs
Laykold® Advantage Gel
The revolutionary new cushion court system, the easy to install all-weather court surface with a wide variety of benefits. From recreational to professional athletes
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Laykold® Advantage Float
Laykold® Advantage Float
The premium cutting edge court system with high force reduction reducing injury and fatigue.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Laykold® Advantage 5
Laykold® Advantage 5
The high performing composite court system.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Laykold® Advantage
Laykold® Advantage
The hard wearing long lasting court system.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Cricket
Supergrasse® Cricket
Supergrasse® Cricket
Covering the foundations of community cricket with choices from talented through foundation to an off season wicket cover.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Hockey
Poligras® Tokyo GT
Poligrass® Tokyo GT
Poligras® Tokyo GT® is the new world class and sustainable hockey surface on the market. The application of several innovative technologies has redefined the surface of hockey.
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Poligras® Platinum COOLplus
Poligras® Platinum COOLplus
Platinum COOLplus is the leading system on the market which produces premium performance. Perfect for professional and elite hockey pitches
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Poligras® Olympia COOLplus
Poligras® Olympia COOLplus
The perfect system for both professional and club hockey pitches. Fast moving playability, excellent player comfort.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Poligras® AquaTurf Evolution
Poligras® AquaTurf Evolution
Our leading watered hockey system is a great choice for State Hockey Centres and Regional facilities.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Poligras® H2Oz Coolplus
Poligras® H2Oz Coolplus
The water efficient choice with excellent player movement and accelerating, turning and slowing down.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Poligras® AquaTurf SL
Poligras® AquaTurf SL
The original water-free system. Springlock technology, high wear resistance, low abrasion. Optional dry or wet use.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Indoor Courts
Dynapoint® Classic
Dynapoint® Classic
Your superior, hygienic, easy to clean choice for indoor sports and multi-functional surfaces from Olympic to recreational standards.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Netball
Laykold® Advantage Gel
Laykold® Advantage Gel
The revolutionary new cushion court system, the easy to install all-weather court surface with a wide variety of benefits. From recreational to professional athletes
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Laykold® Advantage Float
Laykold® Advantage Float
The premium cutting edge court system with high force reduction reducing injury and fatigue.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Laykold® Advantage 5
Laykold® Advantage 5
The high performing composite court system.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Laykold® Advantage
Laykold® Advantage
The hard wearing long lasting court system.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Rugby
LigaTurf® RS+260 COOLplus
LigaTurf® RS+260 COOLplus
Our "One Turf" system provides the best solution for Rugby for both professional and training facilities. Suitable for Soccer and AFL.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
LigaTurf® HB260
LigaTurf® HB260
The best value AFL playing surface suitable for all levels of play.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Soccer
LigaTurf® HB250
LigaTurf® HB250
Our budget priced, workhorse surface, this economical solution offers the ultimate look, feel and longevity.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
LigaTurf® HB260
LigaTurf® HB260
Our top of the range soccer surface with enhanced performance and outstanding durability.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
LigaTurf® RS+260 COOLplus
LigaTurf® RS+260 COOLplus
Our "One Turf" system provides the best solution for Rugby for both professional and training facilities. Suitable for Soccer and AFL.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Tennis – Grass Courts
Supergrasse® Tennis
Supergrasse® Tennis
From amateur to professional our Supergrasse Tennis systems provide unsurpassed value are suitable for all climates and mimics the best natural lawn courts.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Tennis – Hard Courts
Laykold® Masters Gel
Laykold® Masters Gel
The revolutionary technologically advanced, seamless cushioned court system with 17%+ player performance force reduction, true fence-to-fence cushioning!
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Laykold® Masters Float
Laykold® Masters Float
The premium cutting edge system with 21% force reduction made from recycled tennis balls with a prefabricated shockpad for advanced player comfort.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Laykold® Masters 5
Laykold® Masters 5
14% force reduction court made from recycled tennis balls, has consistent ball bounce, reliable footing and staying power.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Laykold® Masters
Laykold® Masters
Our factory textured system has simplified the installation process resulting in a consistent surface pace no matter the location or applicator.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Tennis – Clay Courts
Policlay® Turf
Policlay® Turf
The waterless synthetic clay system.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Policlay® Pave
Policlay® Pave
The all weather clay court system.
Download Product Brochure
Technical Specifications
Order Sample
View full info
Recreation
Lawns & Landscapes
Classic GT
Classic 35
Contact
Search for:
search
Privacy Policy & Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy & Terms and Conditions
Home
Pages
Privacy Policy & Terms and Conditions
The Advanced Polymer Technology Pty Ltd  (APT) website (www.aptasiapacific.com.au), Sports by APT website (www.sportsbyapt.com), the Laykold subdomain (http://ebinder.sportsbyapt.com/), APT Industrial website (www.industrialbyapt.com), Qualideck subdomain (http://ebinder.industrialbyapt.com/) and Home By APT website (www.homebyapt.com), collectively (the “Websites”) are operated by APT – Advanced Polymer Technology Pty Ltd, located at Factory 3, Dunlopillo Drive, Dandenong South, Victoria, Australia (“APT” or “we”). We take the private nature of your personal information very seriously and this Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit or use the Websites.  Please read this notice very carefully.Children’s PrivacyChildren under 18 years of age are not permitted to use the Websites for any purpose and APT does not collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 18.  If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 18, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from a child under 18, please contact us.Visitors to the WebsiteWhen you submit a request via the  Contact or Request Information forms on the website you may voluntarily provide us with certain information about yourself.  This can include name, email address, contact information, details of your request and any other information you provide us.  We also collect records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.  If you’re visiting the Websites on your mobile device, you may also choose to provide us with location data.Website Access InformationLike most website operators, APT collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request when visitors use the Websites. APT’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how APT’s visitors use or visit the Websites. From time to time, APT may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its Websites.  APT also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to the Websites. For instance, APT may monitor the Websites to help identify spam.  We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioural tracking).  APT may use publicly available information to match a user’s IP address with a corporate address to better understand user interest in the Websites.In addition to log data, we may also collect information about the device you’re using to access the Websites, including the type of device, the operating system, device settings, device identifiers and crash data. Whether we collect some or all of this information often depends on what type of device you’re using and its settings.  To learn more about the information your device makes available to us, please review the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider.We do not collect personal information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.Cookies and Web BeaconsLike many websites, the Websites may use “cookies” to collect information.  A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. APT may use cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of the Websites, and their website access preferences. Website visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Website, with the drawback that certain features of the Websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. Certain features of our Websites may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Websites. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies.Pages of our Websites may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).Google AnalyticsThe Websites use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies to help analyse how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Websites (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers within the United States. Google will use this information on our behalf for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Websites, compiling reports on website activity and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. The IP-address that your Browser conveys within the scope of Google Analytics, will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. You can also opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics with effect for the future by downloading and installing Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on for your current web browser: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=enHow We Use Your InformationWe use the information we collect to provide you full access and functionality of the Websites.  Accordingly, your information may be used for the following purposes: (i) to provide and improve our services, features and content; (ii) to administer your use of our services and accounts; (iii) to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Websites; (iv) to better understand your needs and interests; (v) to fulfill requests or to respond to questions or comments you may make; (vi) to personalise your experience; (vii) to provide you with announcements, notifications and advertisements related to your interests and use of the Websites and other communications such as electronic newsletters, promotional e-mails or similar messaging; (viii) to provide service announcements; (ix) to protect against users seeking to hack into the Websites; (x) to assess the level of general interest in the Websites and (xi) for any other purpose with your consent.How We Share your InformationWe may disclose non-personally identifiable aggregated information about our users without restriction.If you use the Websites to request a quote, we may share information, such as your name, email address, phone number, job site and specifics about your job with a third party contractor who are requested to use your information only to the extent reasonably necessary to respond to your request.   [BD1]Except as otherwise provided in this policy, we disclose the potentially personally-identifying information you disclose to APT only to those of our employees, contractors and affiliated organisations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide Websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organisations may be located outside of your home country and by using the Websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations or as described above, we disclose personally-identifying only when required to do so by law, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of APT, third parties or the public at large.  If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users.In addition, in some cases we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if APT or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that APT goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of APT may continue to use your personal and non-personal information only as set forth in this policy. Otherwise, we will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.We may also disclose your personally-identifying information if you expressly consent to the disclosure.Your Access to and Control Over your InformationWe strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:•         Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.•         Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by clicking “email preferences” at the bottom of our emails, contacting us via the help email address info@aptasiapacific.com.au , or calling 1800 652 548 or +61 3 8792 8000.  If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions. This opt out does not apply to information provided to the Company as a result of a product purchase, warranty registration, product service experience or other transactions.Accessing, Correcting and Deleting Your Information You may contact us to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We may not be able to delete your personal information without also deleting your user account.We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.Your Australian Privacy Rights  Users of our Websites that are Australian residents can request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us, or write us at:APT Asia Pacific Pty LtdPO Box 4260Dandenong SouthVictoria, Australia.Security We are committed to protecting your personal information. We regularly test our facilities and use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure.Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Websites. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Websites.Links and Third-Party SitesOur Websites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our sites and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.The Websites may use interfaces with social media sites such as Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and others.  If you choose to “like” or share information from the Websites through these services, you should review the privacy policy of that service. If you are a member of a social media site, the interfaces may allow the social media site to connect your site visit to your personal information.Changes to this Privacy PolicyAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, APT may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We will post the updated policy on the Websites and, if required by law, further notify you of the changes.  In all cases, use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. Please check this policy frequently for updates and changes.  If you continue to visit or use the Websites after those changes are in effect, you agree to the revised policy.Questions and contact informationIf you would like to access, correct, amend, or delete any personal information we have about you please contact APT, call 1800 652 548 or +61 3 8792 8000, or by mail at PO Box 4260, Dandenong South, Victoria, Australia.
QuicklinksNews Specifiers Agents Contact Privacy & Terms ConnectFacebook Twitter LinkedIn Contact
Phone:+61 (3) 8792 8000
Office hours:Mon-Fri: 8:30am – 5:00pm
ABN – 72 066 046 231
Map
Site by Cooper Westwood | Copyright © 2020 APT Asia Pacific. All Rights Reserved. | Privacy PolicyFacebook Twitter LinkedIn
